let's see four iconic proofs without
words in under 60 seconds by using two
triangular arrays of unit squares to
form an N by n +1 rectangle we see that
the sum of the first n positive integers
is equal to n * n + 1 / 2 next by using
four congruent right triangles to
partially fill a square diagram and then
measuring empty space in two different
ways by moving Triangles around we see
that c^2 = A2 + B2 where A and B are the
legs of a right triangle with hypotenuse
C third by rotating the bottom half of
odd Stacks around their central element
we obtain a square showing that the sum
of the first n positive odd integers is
n s and finally by taking a 1x one unit
square and repeatedly shading half of
the unshaded remaining area we get a
formula for the infinite sum of the
powers of 1/2 in particular this
infinite sum is one